[RESEARCHER]
Lena was married to, uh, this
guy named Frank Ford, but that,
[RESEARCHER]
that would have been the line, the
through line is through Jim Hurd, Lena,
[RESEARCHER]
and then Burt Ford.
[CLERK]
Yeah, and that-- I guess that, you
know, I guess that's what I'm saying.
[CLERK]
So like for example, if Burt
never had a succession-
[RESEARCHER]
Mm-hmm
[CLERK]
... you know, to get any... And, and once
again, I don't know what you're doing, you
[RESEARCHER]
Right
[CLERK]
... as far as like, you know, trying
to figure the land out and stuff.
[CLERK]
But like, you know, at that point it's just
gonna stay in his name if he ha- he never
[CLERK]
had a succession. So it's not gonna be passed
down to any of his children or anything like
[CLERK]
that because there isn't any legal vehicle to
do that if they didn't do some type of a
[RESEARCHER]
Right.
[CLERK]
Unless he had already donated
it or given, you know,
[CLERK]
donated the property or
got it out of his name-
[RESEARCHER]
Right
[CLERK]
... somehow. Let me go pull this one
thing and I'll be right back, okay?
[RESEARCHER]
All right. Thank you. Thank you.
[CLERK]
All right. Thanks.
You
[CLERK]
there?
[RESEARCHER]
I'm here.
[CLERK]
Yeah, this is a pretty substantial
amount of paper here on Jim.
[laughs]
[CLERK]
Not a ton, but a, a good bit.
Um-
[RESEARCHER]
Jim had a lot going on
[laughs]
[CLERK]
So basically you're... So basically you're
looking for the judgment of possession. Let's
[RESEARCHER]
Right. Uh, if... Yeah, if
there's something that...
[RESEARCHER]
'Cause I'm, uh, what I'm thinking
is it sounds like Lena Hurd passed
[RESEARCHER]
and he didn't have any children, so it
kind of dispersed out to his siblings,
[RESEARCHER]
which Lena would've been one of
his siblings i- in theory or Math-
[CLERK]
Right
[RESEARCHER]
... or Mathina.
[clears throat]
[CLERK]
Uh, let me see if I can find the
judgment of possession in here.
[RESEARCHER]
Okay. Or anything-
[CLERK]
So far, no
[RESEARCHER]
... anything with Burt Ford or
Forge or anything like that.
[CLERK]
All right. So the, the...
Margaret Bursey and Mattie Tannehill.
[CLERK]
Do you know... Do those names sound familiar?
[RESEARCHER]
Yeah, those are his sisters. Yes.
[CLERK]
Okay. So that's what I see.
Um...
[CLERK]
Okay.
So yeah, it looks like Burt here comes into
it al- a- along with many, many others,
[CLERK]
nieces and nephews. They filed an opposition
to the application for administration.
[RESEARCHER]
Hmm.
[CLERK]
So,
I mean, it's like on petition to Annie Bell,
Adams, Mary Ford Jenkins, California Ford,
[CLERK]
Boyd, Burt Ford, Manish Ford, Mary Lurgin
Anderson, all residents of Claiborne Parish,
[CLERK]
Frank Ford, residing in Oeltown, Arkansas,
William Phillips, resident in Muskogee,
[CLERK]
Alabama, and Willip Lurgin residing in El
Dorado, Arkansas, that your opponents are the
[CLERK]
nieces and nephews of decedent aforesaid,
and they r- you know, relists them.
[CLERK]
So there's several of them there.
[RESEARCHER]
Okay.
[CLERK]
Um, so they, they filed that,
and then
[CLERK]
here's the answer to the
opposition and then...
[sighs]
[CLERK]
I'm looking to see.
I don't see a judgment of possession in here,
[CLERK]
which is what, you know, it
would be today. Once again-
[RESEARCHER]
Right
[CLERK]
... this is 1930,
1940.
[CLERK]
Um-
[RESEARCHER]
Well, it'll show that he
was in the fight. Okay.
[laughs]
[paper rustling]
[RESEARCHER]
I really appreciate you doing this.
[CLERK]
Yeah, yeah, sure thing. Um.
[paper rustling]
[CLERK]
You know, I, I just don't
see anything doing that.
[RESEARCHER]
Right.
[CLERK]
Now, I will tell you this, there's
something in here that says this,
[CLERK]
um,
"In this cause, by reason
of the law and the evidence,
[CLERK]
ordered and judgment decree
that Margaret Bursey,
[CLERK]
administratrix of the succession of James
Hurd, be and hereby is authorized and
[CLERK]
to sell for cash to the persons named and the
property described at the price named in the
[CLERK]
petition as prayed for all at the cost of
the succession." Now, I, I don't see that,
[CLERK]
but I mean,
you know-
[RESEARCHER]
Mm
[CLERK]
... it looks like she
was authorized to sell.
[RESEARCHER]
Right. Right.
[CLERK]
Um, hold on. Here's something right here.
Um, "The petitioner has offered to but
said property not all from one person.
[CLERK]
Uh, R.S. buying her to buy a mare and
a colt." Now these are all movables.
[CLERK]
Um.
[paper rustling]
[RESEARCHER]
So interesting.
[CLERK]
Um, ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma-ma.
Yeah, see, I just, I, I don't see anything
where it looks like land transferred-
[RESEARCHER]
Mm-hmm
[CLERK]
... from anyone to anyone.
Um,
[CLERK]
and you know, that would
be the way that like...
[CLERK]
I mean, that's, that's how
somebody has possession of it.
[RESEARCHER]
Right. And that's the connection I'm
trying to, to find that bridge between
[RESEARCHER]
Jim, uh, Burt,
and just try to fill that gap.
[RESEARCHER]
'Cause it's been weird in our
family the whole entire time.
[RESEARCHER]
We, Lena doesn't have a death
certificate that we can find,
[RESEARCHER]
so she basically disappears after 1910.
And, um, we don't know what happened to her.
[RESEARCHER]
And, uh, and then you have
Burt, and then you have Burt,
[RESEARCHER]
um, mentioning the Jim Hurd estate
in his will.
[RESEARCHER]
So I-
[CLERK]
Right
[RESEARCHER]
... I'm just trying to make that connection.
[CLERK]
Well, it sounds, it sounds like
this was not a very happy family.
[RESEARCHER]
Yeah.
[laughs]
[RESEARCHER]
Right.
[CLERK]
Um-
[RESEARCHER]
A lot of fighting
[CLERK]
... it says here, this is
just like on the opposition,
[CLERK]
"Defendant in opposition admits that the
parties named are heirs of James Hurd,
[CLERK]
but by no means are they all the heirs.
Uh, they oppose the
[CLERK]
selling. Defendant in opposition to answer to
paragraph six denies that the opponent, Annie
[CLERK]
Belle Lusien Adams, is the proper person to be
appointed to make an administratrix of the
[CLERK]
for the reasons that the heirs of the estate
do not desire that she be appointed in that
[CLERK]
petition. In opposition, she joined
Mary Ford, Jenkins Caledonia Ford, Boyd
[CLERK]
Burt Ford, Menish Ford, Larry Lusien Anderson,
Williams, and possibly all the others
[CLERK]
without their knowledge and
consent, and that they have no...
[CLERK]
And they have no objection to
Richard Green be appointed.
[CLERK]
That Annie Belle Lusien
cannot handle the matter.
[CLERK]
She's not capable of doing so, even though
she's lived on the property for a long time,
[CLERK]
and that the deceased, Jim Hurd, did
appreciate during his lifetime the way that...
[CLERK]
did not appreciate, or he did
appreciate the way she treated him-
[RESEARCHER]
Mm-hmm
[CLERK]
... and frequently, frequently
stated that she did,
[CLERK]
that he did not want Annie Belle Lusien Adams
to have anything to do with the handling of
[CLERK]
Um, so it looks like it was contested,
and maybe that's the reason that this
[CLERK]
thing drew out as long as it did.
You know what I mean?
[RESEARCHER]
Right. Right.
[CLERK]
'Cause I would expect, you know, there to
have been a judgment of possession in here.
[CLERK]
I just don't, I just don't see it.
So, um, now look, here's the bonus for you.
[CLERK]
You make it out to that really nice
weather you got out there in Utah,
[CLERK]
and come here where it's about
ninety-nine or a hundred degrees-
[laughs]
[CLERK]
... and about eighty percent humidity.
You can come here and
search these little records-
[RESEARCHER]
I will
[CLERK]
... to your heart's content.
[RESEARCHER]
Hey, well, you did more than
enough, and I sure do appreciate it.
[CLERK]
All right, man. Well, listen,
good luck to you, okay?
[RESEARCHER]
All right. Thank you so much.
[CLERK]
Take care of yourself. All right. Bye.
[RESEARCHER]
All right. You too. Bye.
[phone clicks]